The Princess Sapphire
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Princess Knight,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Fourteenth Episode
The Love Letters
It's finished! Finally it's finished!
My camera is finished!
My beautiful camera!
Now I want to try it.
I have to strike a pose! I'll
slip on a suitable outfit and...
I must hurry! The
self-timer is on!
Why isn't it going off?
Hey, Garigori! I heard
that you invented...
...a strange mechanism that
quickly makes small portraits.
Would this be it?
Yes, that's the one, Baron.
But what the hell is in here?! Hey, what are
you doing standing up there like a statue?
But what is this crackling?
Well done, Prince Sapphire! I see that
today you are studying hard. Well done! Well done!
Keep it up.
Dear Sapphire, I had a lot of fun
the other day, with you,
at the carnival party.
It was one of the most beautiful things
I have ever witnessed.
Furthermore, on that same day,
I met a beautiful girl,
who has remained in my heart.
If you remember, she was the girl
I danced with.
I would immensely like
to be able to meet her again.
Therefore, I beg you to find her.
...and arrange a meeting with her
on my behalf.
Best regards.
Prince Franz.
How stupid! The girl he
met was actually me.
Well, Your Highness!
An hour has already passed.
You have studied enough for today.
I want to reward you
for your diligence.
- What has he prepared for me?
- If you stand still for a moment,
I will take a nice picture of you
with my brand-new camera.
Please, Prince,
don't make me waste time!
As you wish!
- No, wait! Don't go!
- So, have you decided?
I could take it with this
headpiece and with this girl's dress.
- Oh, no!
- I know I can't.
Prince Sapphire, a photo
of you dressed up like this...
...would make it obvious
that you are a girl!
This photo could even fall into
the hands of Grand Duke Duralumin!
What a tragedy would
that be for our kingdom?
And what would you want
to do with this photo, anyway?
I won't tell you! It's
none of your business.
I know how you feel, Your Highness.
I know how difficult it is for you
to pretend to be a boy...
...while you are, in reality,
a beautiful young girl!
All right, I want to please you!
I will take one for you just how you want it.
- Poor little thing...!
- Thank you, Garigori!
What a serious look!
But I think Prince Franz will still
like this photo anyway.
"To Prince Franz,
in the kingdom of Terradoro".
Opal!
Go mail
this letter for me!
Well, well!
Darn, I can't reach it!
Oh, yes! There we go!
Thank you, little horse!
You were really kind!
I would like to know
the contents of the letter...
...that Sapphire had Opal mail!
You see to it, 0017!
Don't worry, Baron Nylon.
It will be a piece of cake.
First of all,
I will use disguise number 85.
Voilà!
A spy's first task
is to steal other people's mail.
Hey, is everyone in this village
a graphomaniac!
This one is going to a Prince.
Second task:
if nothing was found,
return the mail,
so as not to arouse suspicion.
End of the disguise!
Good secret agent, huh?
You say there wasn't
any letter from Sapphire?
It's absolutely impossible!
I checked all the letters
one by one!
There was no suspicious letter
addressed to Prince Franz.
But then, maybe, this was it!
Did you check it well?
- I hope you opened it.
- Yes! And inside I found...
..a photograph
of a beautiful girl!
Idiot! That was exactly the one
I was looking for! Go get it!
At your command!
I'm going to redo the job!
I'm flying!
When I have that photo..
Excuse me, Your Highness,
what did you do with that photo?
Be careful not to lose it,
please.
It could be dangerous.
These are unsafe times
Why? What happened?
They ambushed a mail coach
and robbed it!
- What?!
- You're scaring me like that!
- Where did they attack him?
- I heard it was...
...at the North pasture.
- Oh, no!
They're looking for my letter!
Let's go!
Damn wind!
It's driving me crazy!
I didn't imagine it would
be so exhausting being a spy!
There, I got it! No! This
one is slipping away, damn it!
I feel like I'm going crazy!
- Who's coming?
- Here's who took the letters!
Drop that sack!
My sack!
Sorry, but it's still mine!
He took it back!
Third task: climb trees!
Damned meddler! I'll
make you fall from this tree!
Fourth task: never fall!
Fifth task:
escape the enemy by any means!
- Bye-bye! See ya!
- He's getting away, damn it!
- Wait!
- I can't wait!
I have an urgent appointment!
- Fine, you asked for it!
- No! Not the anti-aircraft, please!
My father used to tell
me not to aim too high!
Stop, little goat! Give
me back that letter!
- A goat?!
- Come here, be good!
Goats like paper.
- Yeah! She'll eat the letter!
- Come, Opal!
Stop, you damned eater
of mail!
Fourth task of a spy: in
case of emergency, jump!
Wait!
Excuse me,
I'm in a bit of a hurry!
The road forks here.
Where did they go?
What? How come I don't see her anymore?
Where did she end up
that damned goat?
Open up, my children!
I am your mother!
It's mommy!
Come on in, mommy!
- Hi, mom!
- Hi, mom! Mommy!
- We missed you!
- Mommy!
I missed you so much.
I hope you didn't let
anyone in while I was away.
Oh, no, mom! No one!
There are very bad men
around, so be careful.
- Yes, mom!
- This is your dinner
What do you think of it?
Open up!
I'll get in through there.
I guess that means
I'll have to imitate Santa Claus.
Cheer up! Santa Claus is coming!
Santa Claus is coming!
He'll come down the chimney!
He's a bad man! Hide!
A man?!
Here is Santa Claus!
I was passing by this way
and I said to myself:
"Why not pay a little visit
to this lovely little family?"
How strange,
he leaves wolf tracks!
And yet only that goat
passed by here.
This house is too solid!
Clever, these goats!
Look, a crack!
I've found the weak spot.
Now I'll take care of it.
It's wide enough to see
inside. Here are the letters!
They look delicious! I'm going
to eat them right away! Yes, yes!
No! Don't eat that
letter! Please, wait! Stop!
If mom sees you, she'll scold you!
What do I do now? I have
to give her something else!
I don't have paper, I only
have money! I have no choice.
Look, little goat! This is
much better than the letter!
Here! Taste it, come on! Eat!
There goes 10,000 Scudi!
Good! Will you give me some more?
What?! Those weren't enough for you?
If you don't give them
to me, I'll eat this letter
Stop! Please, no! Enough!
I'll give you more! Here, take it!
I can't watch...
- More, please!
- Here!
One more!
Damn it, I don't have any more!
I'm ruined!
Well, children! Since that man
has gone, we can eat.
Great! I was so hungry!
Open up! Open, damn wolf!
I realized that you are actually a wolf
and you disguised yourself as a goat!
I recognized your footprints!
You won't manage to trick me! Open up!
He climbed onto the roof!
He wants to get in through the chimney!
Where could they have hidden?
Don't eat our dinner! No!
You're here!
No!
- Mama!
- Mommy!
Let me go! Let me go! No!
Mommy!
Don't let the little goats find out
who I really am!
- What?!
- He's coming here!
Why do you live with the little goats,
you who are a she-wolf?
Now I will tell you why.
My husband is the master of the woods
Some time ago he devoured
the mother of those little goats,
then he ordered me
to stay with his children
So I disguised myself as a goat
and now I live with them.
Now I understand: you act like a goat
so as not to raise suspicion!
That's right! My husband wants
me to fatten up the kids well for him...
...before eating them.
You know, I've raised them until now...
...as if I were their mother
and they believe I'm the real one.
They love me. No one, before,
had loved me so much...
.and I treat them like my own children.
Mind you tell me the truth,
otherwise...
Believe me,
I've grown fond of them too
I love them
as if they were wolf pups.
So much so that when my husband
comes to ask for them,
I won't let him take them!
I will defend their little lives
even at the cost of my own!
This whole story has moved me!
But a spy
shouldn't get emotional!
I will take advantage of the situation
and go get the letters!
- What is it?
- It's my husband coming!
He is coming here because the time has come for him
to devour the kids!
What can I do?!
She-wolf, can I kill him?
If this can save the kids,
yes
Good heavens!
Have you fattened the kids?
How scary!
Yes, of course.
I fattened them just as you wanted.
Do you think they are big enough?
Yes, my husband.
You look so much like a goat that I
feel like eating you too!
Take this!
With an injured tongue,
I can no longer eat the kids!
That bad guy
will eat our mother!
Without a sword he won't make it!
Help!
You will pay for this!
If he runs into me..!
I've been traveling for a long time,
looking for a beautiful landscape...
...to immortalize in a
beautiful photograph!
What do I see! It's a great subject!
This photo will be a masterpiece!
Damn it!
The Prince is in trouble!
This tree will stop him!
It's me: Garigori!
Prince Sapphire!
Hold on, I'm coming to help you!
Charge!
I will use my photographic weapons!
You hit him! Good!
And now it's my turn!
- I did it! Thanks, Garigori!
- The enemy has been defeated!
- Thanks to you! - I'm happy
that you are safe, Your Highness.
Meanwhile, secret agent 0017
hasn't been sitting idle!
I got all the letters!
Here is the one I was looking for!
I'll run and take it to the Baron!
He's running away with our dinner!
Stop, you dirty thief!
It's our dinner!
Give us back our dinner!
Oh! The letters!
Good heavens!
That's our dinner!
Our dinner!
Give us back our meal!
Our dinner! Dinner!
I'll get out of your way immediately!
But you...!
Yes, little goats,
I am just as you see me.
- I am a she-wolf.
- Mama, I don't care who you are.
- You are always my mama.
- What?!
Yes, mama! Come eat
dinner with us! Come! Come!
Do you still believe I am your mother
despite my terrible appearance?
Yes, mama! You are still
our mama!
How sweet you are, my children
Mama! Mommy!
Now, little ones,
eat peacefully.
Thank you, mama.
How delicious!
Tell me: do you like it?
Now we will take a keepsake photo!
Gather together in a group, everyone!
Did you see, Garigori?
Even a she-wolf...
...can take the appearance
of a goat and save the little ones.
I too will continue to pretend
to be a boy...
...to save my people.
Farewell, friends!
- Goodbye!
- Thank you!
- Bye! Bye!
- Bye!
- Goodbye!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP